midnitespot.com 2008-12-17

# Mid Nite Spot ™ - The Nite Does Not Have To End

| 

Untitled Document | 

MidNiteSpot Privacy Policy  
  
---  
   
What This Privacy Policy Covers  
•  | This policy covers how MidNiteSpot treats personal information that MidNiteSpot collects and receives, including information related to your past use of MidNiteSpot’s website. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.   
• | This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MidNiteSpot does not own or control, or to people that MidNiteSpot does not employ or manage.   
   
Information Collection and Use  
• | MidNiteSpot collects personal information when you register with MidNiteSpot, in order to view MidNiteSpot members only pages. MidNiteSpot may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.  
  
•

| When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. When making purchases through MidNiteSpot, you will be directed to PayPal. You can view their policy at the following link:  
PayPal Policy (<http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside>). Once you register with MidNiteSpot and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.  
• | MidNiteSpot automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request.  
• | MidNiteSpot uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.   
   
Information Sharing and Disclosure  
• | MidNiteSpot does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
|   | º | We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MidNiteSpot under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help MidNiteSpot communicate with you about offers from MidNiteSpot and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.  
---|---|---  
º | We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;   
º | We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MidNiteSpot's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
º | We transfer information about you if MidNiteSpot is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MidNiteSpot will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.   
  
\-   
  
• | MidNiteSpot displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.   
|   | º | MidNiteSpot does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.   
---|---|---  
º | MidNiteSpot advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).   
•  | MidNiteSpot works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.   
   
Cookies  
•  | MidNiteSpot may set and access MidNiteSpot cookies on your computer.   
• | MidNiteSpot lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MidNiteSpot's cookies.   
•  | MidNiteSpot uses web beacons to access MidNiteSpot cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with MidNiteSpot products and services.  
   
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences  
•  | If you would like to edit your MidNiteSpot registration information, please send an email to [contactus@midnitespot.com](mailto:%20contactus@midnitespot.com).  
• | We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MidNiteSpot service, such as event and service announcements, administrative messages and the MidNiteSpot Newsletter, that are considered part of your MidNiteSpot account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.   
• | You can delete your MidNiteSpot information, please send an email to [contactus@midnitespot.com](mailto:%20contactus@midnitespot.com).  
   
Confidentiality and Security   
• | We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.   
• | We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.  
   
Changes to this Privacy Policy  
• | MidNiteSpot may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MidNiteSpot account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.   
   
Questions and Suggestions   
• | If you have questions or suggestions, please send an email to [contactus@midnitespot.com](mailto:%20contactus@midnitespot.com) or you can contact us at:   

MidNiteSpot, L.L.C.  
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues  
PO Box 475  
New York, NY 10028-9998  
(212) 380-1192  

|   
  
---
